#### Contact

loridthornton@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lori-thornton-pmhnp-bc-rn-mba-71a10417 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare Management
Patient Safety
Team Building

# Lori Thornton, PMHNP-BC, RN, MBA

Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner-BC

Greater Atlanta Area

## Summary

My passion is taking care of people and creating a better environment for both my patients and my coworkers. I strongly believe in innovation and creating authentic and relevant change-practices. My background is vast, with nearly 15 years providing direct and indirect patient care in the following areas: acute-psych, Geri-psychiatric, ECT, acute/ER at a charity hospital, PICU, CC, rehabilitation, medical-surgical, pediatrics, home health, and management in long-term care.

## Experience

Medical Solutions
Travel Nurse
April 2020 - Present (3 months)
New York, United States

**Acute Care** 

Eastside Medical Center Nurse Manager December 2018 - April 2020 (1 year 5 months) Snellville, Georgia, United States

Acute/Adult Psychiatric & ECT

Peachford Behavioral Health House Supervisor May 2018 - February 2019 (10 months) Atlanta, Georgia

Magnolia Consulting

Owner

August 2011 - September 2018 (7 years 2 months)

Gonzales, Louisiana

#### Consulting

Our Lady of the Lake Charge Nurse (Acute Med-Surg/Telemetry/Psychiatric) July 2016 - August 2018 (2 years 2 months) Behavioral Health

Southeast Louisiana Home Health, LLC Home Health Nurse April 2016 - January 2018 (1 year 10 months) Hammond, Louisiana

Our Lady of the Lake Regional Medical Center Float Pool RN 2009 - 2012 (3 years)

Comcare Health Services
Assistant Director Of Nursing/Interim DON
March 2007 - February 2009 (2 years)
Baton Rouge, Louisiana Area

Earl K. Long Medical Center Charge Nurse (Med/Surg) July 2005 - February 2008 (2 years 8 months)

Our Lady of the Lake Regional Medical Center Staff RN (Rehabilitation)& Float Pool April 2002 - February 2007 (4 years 11 months)

North Oaks Health System Staff RN (Float) January 2003 - August 2006 (3 years 8 months) Hammond, Louisian

### Education

Walden University

Nurse Practitioner, MSN-Psychiatric Mental Health, Psychiatric/Mental Health Nurse/Nursing · (2018 - 2020)

Herzing University

MSN - Family Nurse Practitioner · (2017 - 2018)

Louisiana State University and Agricultural and Mechanical College Bachelor of Science (BS), Business & History

Our Lady of the Lake College

Bachelor's degree/Studied Health Service Administration, Registered Nursing/ Registered Nurse

Univeristy of Phoeix and LSU MBA